<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Open source on myhightech.org</title><link>https://myhightech.org/categories/open-source/</link><description>Recent content in Open source on myhightech.org</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://myhightech.org/categories/open-source/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Learning stuff: Pulumi for AWS</title><link>https://myhightech.org/posts/20210915-pulumi-check/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://myhightech.org/posts/20210915-pulumi-check/</guid><description>I decided to make a habit of learning at least one new tool, technology every month and prepare a blog post about it. In recent months I focused mostly on the stuff I was dealing at work. Right now I&amp;rsquo;m reading &amp;ldquo;Atomic Habits&amp;rdquo; by James Clear, so that&amp;rsquo;s the first habit I would like to create. :)
What is Pulumi This month I decided to check out Pulumi. Pulumi is an open-source infrastructure as code tool.</description></item><item><title>Running OpenEBS on a Odroid HC4 cluster</title><link>https://myhightech.org/posts/20210530-openebs-on-odroid-hc4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://myhightech.org/posts/20210530-openebs-on-odroid-hc4/</guid><description>I bought recently two Odroid HC4 microcomputers and 4 Seagate Barracuda 2 TB HDD with the intention to farm Chia on them. The HC4 platform used on ARM64 processor and has two SATA 3, which can be used to plug HDD or SSD drive to it. At work, we are checking out currently the OpenEBS project, which allows to build a Container Attached Storage for Kubernetes using local disks. I was curious, if I could use OpenEBS on those HC4 devices and create a CAS for a Kubernetes home lab.</description></item><item><title>My simple The Elder Scrolls Online addon manager in Rust</title><link>https://myhightech.org/posts/20201228-eso-addon-manager/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://myhightech.org/posts/20201228-eso-addon-manager/</guid><description>I was missing a addon manager for ESO UI on Linux. There is Minion, which I tried to run in the Wine prefix of my ESO installation, but it crashed too often.
What I expected from the addon manager was:
working on Linux command line interface easy to backup the addon configuration So I created eso-addons. It uses a single configuration file for storing the addon configuration, so I can just backup this config file and use it to restore my addons.</description></item><item><title>Build a static web page with Hugo and Amplify</title><link>https://myhightech.org/posts/build-page-with-hugo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://myhightech.org/posts/build-page-with-hugo/</guid><description>Static website hosting You most probably heard about static website hosting, static website generators and Github Pages or Netlify. After the boom of web technologies the backends got heavier and heavier, page loading times increased multiple times. You wanted to create a blog or portfolio website and you had to:
buy a server/VPS buy/install a database buy a domain install the required backend software and configure it ensure the system is patched make backups You either made this by yourself or bought a managed solution from some provider.</description></item></channel></rss>